let questions = [
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Emperor of Man?",
        "choices": ["Karl-Franz II", "Boris Todbringer", "Mannfred von Carstein", "Abaddon the Despoiler"],
        "answer": "1"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the Empire's capital province?",
        "choices": ["Kislev", "Reikland", "The Moot", "Suddenland"],
        "answer": "2"
    },

    {
        "question": "What must be done to a heretic?",
        "choices": ["Pay his salary", "Burn him", "Integrate him into the workforce", "Bring him into counseling"],
        "answer": "2"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who is the Chaotic God of Violence and Bloodshed?",
        "choices": ["Khorne", "Khaine", "Solomon Kane", "Kane"],
        "answer": "1"
    },

    {
        "question": "What doesn't actually exist?",
        "choices": ["Wizards", "Taxes", "Skaven", "Bailiffs"],
        "answer": "3"
    },

    {
        "question": "What are Halflings voracious consumers of?",
        "choices": ["Food", "Living space", "Warpstone", "Pocket change"],
        "answer": "1"
    },

    {
        "question": "What type of Elf isn't there?",
        "choices": ["High Elf", "Sea Elf", "Wood Elf", "Mountain Elf"],
        "answer": "4"
    },

    {
        "question": "Kislevites are famous for riding what in battle?",
        "choices": ["Horses", "Bears", "Wives", "Baba Yagas"],
        "answer": "2"
    },

    {
        "question": "How do Greenskins appear in the world?",
        "choices": ["Standard intercourse", "Tectonic movement", "Spores", "They come with the bailiff"],
        "answer": "3"
    },

    {
        "question": "What was the name of Holy Sigmar's holy mallet?",
        "choices": ["Ghal Maraz", "Mal Gharaz", "Siknt'shredded", "N/A"],
        "answer": "1"
    }
]